[{"answer": "I'm my friend", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I'm my friend", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I work wood. Got a piece of land. Mostly work wood", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " I can clear a field", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Really", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Men? I don't know. I don't even know what a woman should be like. In that place I was called a thistle, twice, by two different men. Both of them", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Somebody said you were enlisting.  Are you", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " If there's a mountain we'll all climb, if there's an ocean we'll all drown", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " If there's a mountain we'll all climb, if there's an ocean we'll all drown", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Did you get a picture made", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You're looking", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "He listens to my heart and I get emotional", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Every time you see the doctor you get melancholy", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "He gives you alcohol and you get emotional", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Thank you.  For your that place, Oh lord, we thank you", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "It was delicious", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "But not to volunteer for the war", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "But not to volunteer for the war", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You've got no spleen", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I need help, I need, I do need help, but I need a laborer", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "The rake", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " It's no wonder you're helpless and hopeless if it takes this long to fix your hair.  Say some more", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "It's appalling what's in my head", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Well that's surely true even in English", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "We can't keep anything", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You can keep those earrings", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I have to keep the bangles. They were my mother's", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " He's got a shit coming on. It's overdue", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Like a Christian", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Take them all and leave the saw. Be a sight more use", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "They love to scrub a man.  Put the water on the boil.  It's my liquor, gets their titties swinging", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I'm looking to get out of this. They drag us back to fight", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Either way we're fucked. Run or don't run", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Last time I checked it was '64", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Twenty six years", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Listen up", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "You got a weapon", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Get me out of this dang thing. My fist's about to drop off", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "No ma'am. I'm begging you. I'm already on my knees, otherwise I'd get down on them", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "I'm changed. People change. War changes people something terrible.  my friend's told you", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I can't disagree with that. I was", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "They fit", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I'll say good night", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Pretty much. These boots are good boots", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Good night", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Your hero's discharge. For mighty outstanding valour", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": " And where, where, where is your house", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Evening, Mrs", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": " Where's that place", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "I'm not surprised. Your man looks played out", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Saw him when", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "In my friend's well. A tunnel of trees. The man like a black smudge in the snow, the sun behind him", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Funny thing is it wasn't the same. The image. It wasn't snowing. And in the well, he was, as if he were falling", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "-- I got no appetite left to be in a room with wounded men", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "It's not a face you recognised", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Your boots, one polished, one not yet polished", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "I'm playing a piano and you're standing outside", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "I'm playing a piano and you're standing outside", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Every day of my waiting", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "No, I think it's I divorce you three times and then you're not married anymore", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "You waited enough. I certainly did. I marry you. I marry you. I marry you", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "I hope that that place boy's been seeing to the animals", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "I was not. I was thinking on swollen udders", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "He dead", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "I give you my gun you'll shoot me dead", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "I will not shoot you, but nor am I walking down that mountain looking over my shoulder for you", "docId": "Cold-Mountain.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "What have you got on your side", "qsentId": 72}]